<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Bull Traders Documentation</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Bull Traders Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gaining Access</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/gaining-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/gaining-access/</guid>
      <description>Gaining Access # Logging into the Wordpress admin dashboard # Head to https://bulltraders.com.my/wp-admin Enter the username and password that I provided to you If you are having difficulty or need assistance regaining access to any of your accounts you may contact me.&#xA;Logging into AWS Lightsail Dashboard # Head to https://lightsail.aws.amazon.com/ls/webapp/home?# Enter the username and password that I provided to you Keeping track of my AWS Bills # Head here: https://console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Content</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/editing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/editing-content/</guid>
      <description>Editing Content # General Content # If you want to change any content on this website, unless explicitly stated on this page, the steps would probably be the following:&#xA;Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re logged into Wordpress admin, then visit the page that you want to edit.&#xA;Click on the &amp;ldquo;Edit with Elementor&amp;rdquo; on the top header bar.&#xA;Scroll to the section that you want to edit, click on it.&#xA;Edit the content on the left sidebar editor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Sellable Products</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/products/</guid>
      <description>Managing Sellable Products # This page is about managing products that you can sell via your online WooCommerce store.&#xA;Keep in mind that although you can also technically manage Events in the same way, I would encourage you to refer to the Managing Events page for Events instead.&#xA;Adding a new sellable Product # Adding a new sellable Product is simple, make sure you follow the steps below:&#xA;On the Wordpress Admin Dashboard, click on Products &amp;gt; Add New.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/events/</guid>
      <description>Managing Events # We have a simple event management system that allows for creating events with:&#xA;Start and End Datetimes Location/Venue field Calendar View Ticketing system integrated with WooCommerce Adding a new Event # Adding a new event is simple, but make sure you follow the steps below:&#xA;On your Wordpress Admin Dashboard, click on Events &amp;gt; Add New Events&#xA;Fill up only the following:&#xA;Title. Description. Put all other miscellaneous information (agenda, speakers, etc.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
